Novi Sad, Serbia

Liudmila Kozlachkova

mobile: +381 62 8144373 telegram: @Coastal_lynx e-mail: n13912@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/n13912

ABOUT ME

I'm a frontend developer who prefers to work with the native JS Pure stack. I can handle complicated rendering cases such as automatic animation creation, graphics, working with video and music, canvas, complex user cases for interface interaction, and other game and user mechanics. Experience writing for mobile web applications and web view, landing pages, and admins.

Using BDD methodology, writing autotests, screenshots tests of interface. Use in my work Safari Simulator and Browserstack.

My Favorite technology stack

Native JS, HTML, CSS, Vue JS, Jest, Mocha js, Cypress, React, TS

Languages: Russian native, English B2

EMPLOYMENT

Senior frontend developer | Tinkoff Bank

December 2017 — currently
Moscow, <u>www.tinkoff.ru</u>
IT, System Integration, Internet, Fintech

Creation web renders for Tinkoff stories, sharing stories, landing page for stories and offers. Working in commands Story Constructor and Tinkoff Polls.

The web-render of stories written by me has been successfully developing for 5 years, and implemented in the authorized zone of Tinkoff bank / Tinkoff business / Tinkoff Invest, PWA application and path of mobile application - for sharing on the social networks.

Public examples of my work include:

https://s.tinkoff.ru/jocery - web puzzle
https://s.tinkoff.ru/ndvedrenth - video
https://s.tinkoff.ru/mousedre - poll with score rating

Frontend developer | Anna Systems

April 2017 — november 2017 Moscow, <u>anna.systems/</u>

IT, System Integration, Internet

Anna Systems is a project that provides access to supercomputers and high-performance computing. My responsibilities include planning and development for the user interface. Interface layout.

Used JavaScript, Vue JS, HTML5, CSS3

Junior Frontend developer | WinLineBet

January 2014 — january 2016 Moscow, <u>winlinebet.com</u>

Projects i have participated:

Creation frontend of the "Live monitors" project (broadcast of online match statistics on displays)
Layout of the "partner office" application, including the addition of Angular Bootstrap components to a new site. Creating JS banners for partner websites.

EDUCATION

Yandex Practicum

Yandex Practicum, Course React Developer, 2021

Bauman Moscow State Technical University

Specialist Center, Javascript course, Website Creation course according to W3C standards in HTML 5 and CSS 3, 2014

Moscow State Academy of Veterinary Medicine and Biotechnology - MVA named after K.I. Skryabin M.S.E in Merchandising, 2006